<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Translation</title>
    <link href="/2023/10/01/Translation/"/>
    <url>/2023/10/01/Translation/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Article 1:<a href="https://www.quora.com/If-there-is-an-infinite-number-of-universes-with-alternative-realities-how-come-there-isnt-one-where-a-form-of-travel-has-been-created-allowing-them-to-contact-us" title="If there is an infinite number of universes with alternative realities, how come there isn&#39;t one where a form of travel has been created allowing them to contact us?"></a></p><p>If there are, there is no connection between them. Almost every theory of why the Big Bang occurred leads to the conclusion that each one creates its very own space-time, so there could be an infinity of universes, but each would be as isolated and unique as if absolutely none of the others existed.</p><p>However, even if other universes existed which were in some way connected to us, there is absolutely no way that we could hope to go to another one, because even at near-light speeds it would take millions or tens of millions of years to even go to the nearest galaxies in our own Universe, and there is absolutely nothing that we can observe that suggests that any portals to other Universes are within billions of light years of us. That means that even if there was a way to get to another Universe, it would take longer than the lifetime of the Sun and Solar System for a spacecraft to get there.</p><p>It’s sort of like an ant in New York wanting to travel to Irkutsk in Siberia. It might be a nice dream, but it isn’t going to happen without dying, going to Heaven, and talking God into sending you there. And actually, it wouldn’t be such a nice dream, because unless the other Universe had exactly the same laws of physics that ours has, we would die the instant we set foot in it; and if it did have the same laws of physics, it would be the same as the ant finding itself right back in New York, because everything would look and behave exactly the same. So if you want to go to another Universe, just sit and meditate so long and so valiantly that eventually you can transmigrate there (not likely, of course, but far more likely than doing it for real).</p><p>This book says they have. It all hinges on our comprehension of dark matter which we cant yet see or measure. Our Elder Brothers Return Validated contactees who attempted to forward information speaking publicly and openly became targets of harassment and bullying by authorities, so not many contactees spoke publicly.<br>My understanding is that there are thousands of people world wide who have had a contactee experience. Some have published. You can find a lot of books at the above site, most are free text.<br>George Adamski was the first documented contactee in 1952.</p><p>The very same reason we have yet to be visited - to the best of my knowledge - by time traveling unicorns who speak English with a strong Bronx accent, or why Bob Dylan didn’t compose the music for Star Wars. Who knows?</p><p>Not all possible things happen in each realm of infinitude, so perhaps the trans multiverse travel to Earth has already taken place on some other Earth.</p><p>The universe (Latin: universus) is all of space and time and their contents, including planets, stars, galaxies, and all other forms of matter and energy. While the spatial size of the entire universe is unknown,it is possible to measure the size of the observable universe, which is currently estimated to be 93 billion light-years in diameter. In various multiverse hypotheses, a universe is one of many causally disconnected constituent parts of a larger multiverse, which itself comprises all of space and time and its contents; as a consequence, ‘the universe’ and ‘the multiverse’ are synonymous in such theories.</p><p>文章1：假如多元宇宙真的存在，为什么另一个世界的“我们”还没接触到我们呢？</p><p>答案就在问题里。无限的宇宙意味着我们只是无限多个宇宙中的一个。假如另一个有智慧生命的宇宙拥有超高的科技水平，他们该如何在无限宇宙里选中特定的我们？ 人们甚至没有彻底掌握“无限”的概念。假如你在一个无限的领域里寻找一个拥有智慧生命的行星，这需要数万亿年才能通过搜索一颗颗天体的方式完成一个宇宙。然后，你就需要花费更多的数万亿年在剩余的宇宙里，宇宙一号，二号，30号，然后30，000，000，000，000，000，000，000，000号，然后。。。你应该知道了。当你完全筋疲力，在搜索中用尽了所有的资源，你意识到你甚至还没有开始搜索无限小数里的宇宙。还有无穷无尽的路要走。</p><p>如果有，两者之间也没有任何的联系。几乎所有关于宇宙大爆炸的理论都可以得出这样的结论：每一个宇宙都创造了自己的时空，所以宇宙才可以是无限的，但每一个都是孤立的，独一无二的，就好像其他宇宙都不存在一样。</p><p>然而，就算其他宇宙有与我们沟通的方式， 我们也没有任何可能去到其他宇宙，因为即使以接近光的速度，我们也需要数百万年乃至数千万年的时间才能去到离我们最近的星系，而且我们也没有观测到任何在我们数十亿年光年内的传送门可以带我们去其他宇宙。这意味着即使我们有方法去到另一个宇宙，花费的时间比太阳和太阳系的寿命还长。</p><p>这就像一只来自纽约的蚂蚁想要爬到西伯利亚的伊尔库茨克。这个梦想很美好，但<br>它不会发生除非来到天堂并让上帝把你送到那儿。而且，这也不会这么美好，因为除非另个宇宙有跟我们完全相同的物理定则，不然我们会在抵达的一瞬间死亡。即使它真的有同样的物理定律，那就和蚂蚁发现自己回到了纽约一样，因为一切事物看起来都完全一样。所以如果你想去另一个宇宙，就做下并长时间冥想，最终你会发现自己转世到了那里。</p><p>这本书说他们做到了。这一切都取决于目前还无法被观测到的暗物质。试图公开信息的联络人成为了骚扰和欺凌的目标，所以没有多少被接触者敢公开发言。</p><p>我的理解是世界上有成千上万的人都有过被接触的距离，而有些信息是公开的。你可以在文章顶部发现很多免费阅读的网站。</p><p>1952年，第一个有记录的被接触者是乔治·亚当斯基。</p><p>据我所知，这也是我们还没被说着浓重布朗克斯口音的英文独角兽旅行者拜访的原因，或者为什么鲍勃·迪伦没有为《星球大战》作曲。谁知道呢?</p><p>并不是所有可能的事情都发生在每个的无限领域，所以跨多元宇宙到地球的旅行可能已经发生在另一个地球上。</p><p>宇宙（拉丁：universus）是所有时间，空间和其内容，包括行星，恒星，星系，和所有其他形式的物质和能量。虽然宇宙的空间大小是未知的，测量可观测宇宙的大小是可行的，目前估计的直径大小为930亿光年。在诸多多元宇宙的假说里，一个宇宙是一个更大的多元宇宙里多个互不相连的部分所组成，而多元宇宙包含所有的时间，地点和它的内容。作为结果，“宇宙”和“多元宇宙”在这些理论里其实是同义词。</p><p>Article 2: <a href="https://www.inverse.com/science/cosmic-ring-of-fire" title="ASTRONOMERS OBSERVE RARE ‘COSMIC RING OF FIRE FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THE EARLY UNIVERSE"></a></p><p>In the vast and every-expanding universe, most galaxies resemble our own. The Milky Way is a spiral galaxy, with a flat rotating disk that contains gas, dust and thousands of stars.<br>However, astronomers recently captured images of a super rare type of galaxy, referred to as a ‘cosmic ring of fire,’ in the early universe that may just change leading theories of how galaxies form and evolve over time.<br>The discovery was detailed in a study published Monday in the journal Nature Astronomy.</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/651974f9c458853aefba1157.png"></p><p>A composite image of the ring galaxy, revealing its unusual shape.Tiantian Yuan&#x2F;Hubble Space Telescope</p><p>The team of researchers used spectroscopic data gathered by the WM Keck Observatory in Hawaii and images recorded by NASA’s Hubble Space Telescope to capture the images of the galaxy.<br>The newly discovered galaxy was dubbed R5519, and is located approximately 11 billion light years away. That means it exists in the early years of the universe, less than 3 billion years after the Big Bang.<br>The study suggests that the galaxy is a collisional ring galaxy, which would make it the first one ever detected in the early Universe. As the name suggests, galaxy R5519 likely formed as a result of a violent collision between two galaxies, which is a 1,000 times more rare than other types of galaxies to be found during the universe’s infancy.<br>“The collisional formation of ring galaxies requires a thin disk to be present in the ‘victim’ galaxy before the collision occurs,” Kenneth Freeman from the Australian National University, and co-author of the study, said in a statement. “The thin disk is the defining component of spiral galaxies: before it assembled, the galaxies were in a disorderly state, not yet recognizable as spiral galaxies.”<br>The galaxy is shaped like a slightly deformed circle with a rather massive hole in the middle.<br>That massive hole stretches across a diameter that is two billion times longer than the distance between the Earth and the Sun, and is about three million times larger than the diameter of the supermassive black hole in the galaxy Messier 87, well-known for the first image ever captured of a black hole in April, 2019.<br>“It is a very curious object that we’ve never seen before,” Tiantian Yuan, a researcher at Australia’s ARC Centre of Excellence for All Sky Astrophysics in 3 Dimensions (ASTRO 3D), and lead author of the new study, said in a statement. “It looks strange and familiar at the same time.”</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/651974fdc458853aefba124d.png"></p><p>An artist’s impression of the cosmic ring fire galaxy in the early universe. James Josephides, Swinburne Astronomy Productions</p><p>The galaxy got its stage name, the ‘cosmic ring of fire’ based on its surrounding ring where most of its galactic activity is taking place. And it’s quite the active galaxy, making stars at a rate that is 50 times greater than that of the Milky Way, according to the researchers.<br>The discovery of the collisional ring galaxy can help scientists better understand how galaxies like the Milky Way came to be. The collision that birthed this galaxy was likely of one with a spiral galaxy like our own since that thin disk is crucial for galaxy formation.<br>The Milky Way is that it is on its own collision course with a neighboring galaxy, Andromeda, where the pair will eventually merge in about 4 billion years or so to form a larger galaxy that may be of a similar size to this ancient beast.</p><p>文章2：天文学家在早期宇宙首次观测到罕见的“宇宙火环”</p><p>科学家观测到一个环状星系，该星系不同于银河系这类旋臂星系，中间是超质量黑洞而周围是一个星系组成的圆环，被科学家称为“宇宙火圈”，它形成于大爆炸后30亿年前，由两个星系剧烈碰撞形成。</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/651974f9c458853aefba1157.png"><br>研究小组利用在夏威夷WM Keck观测台收集到的光学数据和NASA 哈勃天文望远镜收集到的图像去捕获“宇宙火环”的图片。</p><p>这个最新发现的星系被命名为R5519，距离地球大约110亿光年。这意味着它存在于宇宙早期，大爆炸后不到30年。</p><p>研究表明，这个星系是由碰撞产生的环星系，这使它成为了早期宇宙中第一个被探测到的星系。顾名思义，星系R5519很有可能是两个星系猛烈碰撞所生成的，比在宇宙初期发现的其他类型的星系要罕见1000倍。</p><p>该研究的合著者，同时也是来自澳大利亚国立大学的肯尼斯·弗里曼声明环星系的碰撞形成发生在“受害者”星系中有一个圆盘之后。这个圆盘是螺旋星系的决定性因素：在它组装之前，星系处于并不会被认为是螺旋星系的无序状态，</p><p>该星系的形状像一个略微变形的圆圈，并在中间有一个相当大的洞。</p><p>这个大洞横跨一个超过二十亿倍地球和太阳之间距离的直径，而且是三百万倍大于星系Messier 87中超质量黑洞的直径，第一个被人类捕获到图片的黑洞，在2019年的四月。</p><p>“这是一个从未被发现的奇怪物体”澳大利亚ARC三维全天空天体物理学卓越中心(ASTRO 3D)的研究员、这项新研究的主要作者Tiantian Yuan在一份声明中说。“它看起来既奇怪又熟悉。”</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/651974fdc458853aefba124d.png"><br>这是来自史文朋天文制片公司的詹姆斯·约瑟夫斯对宇宙早期环状火星系的印象。</p><p>这个星系的艺名是“宇宙火环”，名字来源于它周围的火环，大部分的星系活动都发生在这个环上。据研究人员称，它是一个相当活跃的星系，产生恒星的速度是银河系的50倍。</p><p>碰撞环星系的发现可以帮助科学家更好地了解像银河系这样的星系是如何形成的。产生这个星系的碰撞很可能是一个像银河系一样的螺旋星系，因为这个薄薄的圆盘对星系的形成至关重要。</p><p>银河系与邻近的仙女星系发生的碰撞将最终在大约40亿年发生，并形成一个大小类似与这个“古老的怪物”的星系。</p><p>Article 3:</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>cosmic_watch</title>
    <link href="/2023/09/30/cosmic-watch/"/>
    <url>/2023/09/30/cosmic-watch/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Location 1：The first floor of the school’s basement (indoor, concrete)</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193341c458853aefa4159a.jpg"><br><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193341c458853aefa415aa.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time: 0.393</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:43, 1:14, 2:5, 3:1</p><p>Time between signals: Lowest:0.397(10), highest:8.34(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:Decreasing trend</p><p>Signal amplitude:Highest: 100, lowest: 3. random amplitude, less data at<br>high amplitudes</p><p>Location 2：The fifth floor of the school’s building (indoor, concrete)</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193341c458853aefa415ba.jpg"><br><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193342c458853aefa415d0.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time: 0.686</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:37, 1:16, 2:6, 3:3</p><p>Time between signals: Lowest:0.367(19), highest:7.70(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:Decreasing trend with a sharp increase in between</p><p>Signal amplitude:Highest: 97.02, lowest: 0.98 random amplitude</p><p>Location 3：Caohejin High-tech park</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193348c458853aefa417b3.jpg"><br><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193348c458853aefa417c3.jpg"><br><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193348c458853aefa417d3.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time: 0.539</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:45, 1:22, 2:8, 3:1</p><p>Time between signals:Lowest:0.429(19), highest:9.00(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:Decrease and Increase</p><p>Signal amplitude:Highest: 96.1, lowest: 0.75 random amplitude, a vacancy<br>in low amplitude</p><p>Location 4：Xuhui Riverside Park</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193348c458853aefa417eb.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193354c458853aefa41b25.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193354c458853aefa41b35.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193354c458853aefa41b45.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time: 0.474</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:47, 1:22, 2:7</p><p>Time between signals: Lowest:0.254(9), highest:5.33(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:No obvious trend</p><p>Signal amplitude: Highest: 97.02, lowest: 2.94 random amplitude</p><p>Location 5：Jing An Temple</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193355c458853aefa41b61.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/6519335ac458853aefa41d68.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/6519335ac458853aefa41d78.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time: 0.293</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:60, 1:20, 2:2</p><p>Time between signals:Lowest:0.420(3), highest:8.83(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:Decreasing and increasing</p><p>Signal amplitude: Highest: 96.02, lowest: 0.91 random amplitude</p><p>Location 6：The bund</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/6519335ac458853aefa41d86.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/6519335ac458853aefa41d9b.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193363c458853aefa4202d.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time:0.592</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:1, 1:26, 2:8, 3:1</p><p>Time between signals:Lowest:0.291(12), highest:6.11(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:A sharp decrease and no obvious trend</p><p>Signal amplitude: Highest: 99.1, lowest: 1 random amplitude</p><p>Location 7：The Oriental Pearl TV Tower</p><p>Image:</p><p><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193363c458853aefa4203b.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193363c458853aefa42059.jpg"><img src="https://pic.imgdb.cn/item/65193363c458853aefa42071.png"></p><p>Average number of signals per sampling time:0.524</p><p>Number of signals(numbers:times): 0:39, 1:15, 2:9</p><p>Time between signals:Lowest:0.477(19), highest:1.017(1). Most data have<br>short interval</p><p>Average time:Seems increase, some sharp drop</p><p>Signal amplitude: Highest: 96.08, lowest: 0.96 random amplitude</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="/2023/09/24/hello-world/"/>
    <url>/2023/09/24/hello-world/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues">GitHub</a>.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><code class="hljs bash">$ hexo new <span class="hljs-string">&quot;My New Post&quot;</span><br></code></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html">Writing</a></p><h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><code class="hljs bash">$ hexo server<br></code></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html">Server</a></p><h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><code class="hljs bash">$ hexo generate<br></code></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html">Generating</a></p><h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><code class="hljs bash">$ hexo deploy<br></code></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/one-command-deployment.html">Deployment</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
